(Sheldon:)And you haven't fallen
hopelessly in love with me?
(Amy:)Don't be absurd.
(Amy:)I find the notion
of romantic love
(Amy:)to be an unnecessary
cultural construct
(Amy:)that adds no value to
human relationships.
(Sheldon:)Amy Farrah Fowler, that's
the most pragmatic thing
(Sheldon:)anyone has ever said to me.
(Amy:)I trust this clarification
allows us to return
(Amy:)to boy-slash-friend-slash-
girl-slash-friend status.
(Sheldon:)Of course.
(Sheldon:)Would you like to join me
for Chinese food?
(Amy:)Sheldon, please,
you're suffocating me.
(Sheldon:)My apologies.
(Sheldon:)Good night, Amy.
Good night, Sheldon.
(Howard:)Come on, just
give her a chance.
(Howard:)Maybe she'll grow on you.
(Leonard:)Or maybe she'll finally succeed in
ripping my nuts off.
(Leonard:)There are still 93 ways
she hasn't tried yet.
Look, H-Howard,
I appreciate
(Leonard:)the effort, but this is, like,
the worst date of my life.
(Howard:)Seriously?
(Howard:)I was once robbed by a pre-op
transsexual I met on J-Date,